THE LOVE LAB
THE AFTERNOON
WHEN TWO COUPLES WENT ON DATES
This place looks different.
-We should do a tea ceremony.
-Yeah.
-That color suits you.
-It does?
Thanks.
I usually wear white,
but sometimes I wear bright colors.
Yeah, you do a good job of it.
You draw well too.
Come on. Don't make me blush.
-Wait.
-Do you want to eat something?
-Anything you need?
-Peppermint tea.
How do I get peppermint tea?
-There isn't any.
-I think,
we have to be able to leave.
We have to leave and…
Think of me when you see peppermint tea.
JOOHONEY, CHARLESENTER
Come on!
-Come on, Hye-won.
-I'm saving that comment.
Think of me when you drink hibiscus tea.
I'll remember it.
-You will?
-Yeah, I'll remember.
What the heck?
Think of me when you see peppermint tea.
I'll have to go get it.
I should think of you and pick it up.
-Do you like tea?
-Yeah.
I like herbal tea and fruit tea.
Do you like coffee more, Ha-yoon?
I do like coffee a lot.
Me too.
When I travel, I'd get coffee
from a place that's well-known there.
Maybe you work at a cafe?
WHILE THE TWO SHARE THEIR INTERESTS
Did you just take a picture of me?
So you like taking photos.
Just making memories.
CASUALLY JOINS HIS SELFIE
I have three chins.
It became a goofy photo.
I'm making you shine, aren't I?
Yeah, I like that.
This is nice.
I kind of like this.
What do you like?
-Relaxing?
-Yeah.
It's perfect.
Hurry.
GENTLY
Peace.
What was that?
It took burst shots?
-It looks cute.
-It's cute.
SLIP
-This again?
-Thumbs up.
Heart.
At this rate, they made up their minds.
They took that photo
after making up their minds.
What's up with that?
That's so cute.
Should we light the fire?
Wow!
Awesome.
It's so pretty. Oh, my.
You know, my hands are
-really cold.
-I know.
I have cold hands and feet.
-Really?
-Yeah, it's really bad.
HOLDING IT TIGHT
-Right? Isn't it so bad?
-What's going on?
It's really bad.
It's so cold.
It's so warm. I love it.
Let's go on a date.
Date? I'd love that.
When will we get a chance?
-We'll get one, right?
-Will we?
-We have to make it happen.
-How? Will you become king?
I should become king.
-If I don't, I'll have to win their favor.
-Win their favor?
-What was your first impression of me?
-My first impression of you?
I thought we wouldn't have much in common.
I thought I was really into looks
but after spending a lot of time with you,
I realized that I care
about the personality too.
Wait. Hang on.
When you said you didn't care about looks…
No, looks used to play a huge part for me.
Whose looks did you like
the most at first?
It's you. That's why I chose you at first.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Are you curious about anyone else?
Just you, for now.
There's nobody else besides you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
For now, there's no one.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
There's no one else.
If I went back and voted again?
I'd vote for Jung-min.
I would've grabbed a handful
and never let go.
I think I was drawn to him more
through our conversations than his looks.
At first, he acted more lively
to help break the ice
but he's also very quiet.
I realized he was trying hard
to make everyone feel comfortable.
After realizing that,
I became more attracted to him.
I was thankful to you.
Everyone felt awkward.
It's hard to make such an effort.
Yeah, it's hard for me even now.
You were making an effort.
That's a strength. It's a good thing.
Did you see the photo booth message
-I worked really hard on?
-Yes.
Why no reaction?
Did you really work hard on it?
At first…
-Yeah?
-No,
-I'd rather not say.
-Tell me.
I'll keep that to myself.
Date tomorrow?
I do want to go on a date tomorrow.
I asked who you wanted to go with.
Right, who would I go with?
I hope I become king.
Are you trying to win my favor?
No.
You never mentioned it, did you?
-What?
-What does your ideal type look like?
Do you have one?
My ideal type?
I like someone who has fair skin,
someone who's short rather than tall,
and I like long, straight hair.
Long, black, straight hair.
Someone who's pretty?
I like a pretty woman.
Someone who's pretty and cute.
What is your ideal type?
Someone with a good first impression?
A good… How should I put it?
I got a bit nervous
and felt embarrassed,
so I acted a bit awkward.
I was going to say something nice.
-Yeah?
-You became quiet.
I did feel awkward,
but I really felt shy more than anything.
It was our first date,
so I wanted to impress her.
I didn't want to show her my shy side.
I think I tried very hard
not to show that side of me.
What is it?
To be more exact,
I thought you looked like
someone I'd be attracted to.
-Really?
-Yeah.
We met up with the staff, right?
-You told them your type, right?
-Yeah.
I like someone
who has fair skin and is skinny.
who kind of looks like a baby fox.
Like the actor Lee Jong-suk?
They brought someone who looked
exactly like the guy I described.
-Hello.
Hello.
-Can I sit…
-Please sit wherever you'd like.
I see it.
Even though you're isolated
with your ideal type,
-it may not work out.
-We know it may not.
It may not work out.
As soon as I saw you, I started laughing.
How could they find
someone who looks like that?
It was so surprising
to the point that it made me laugh.
Yeah.
Let's stop here.
The ocean's beautiful.
Yeah, the mountain is tall.
-Hello.
Hello.
Where should we sit?
Eat the fried dish first.
-Okay.
To be honest,
I never had marinated crab before.
-Really?
-Tell me how to eat it.
You just grab it
and suck the meat out.
-It's good if you mix it with rice.
-Mix it with rice?
This is too challenging.
This is like an experiment.
Can they eat messy like this
and still be attracted to each other?
-We are the Love Lab.
-Yeah.
-It's like that.
-We even experiment on eating.
Just suck the meat out.
-It's good.
-How is it?
I've never seen anyone
eat marinated crabs so cutely like that.
"It's good."
I want to act like
I never had marinated crabs either.
Give it a shot.
-Give it a shot?
-Yeah.
-But--
-You want to look cute.
I've never seen this before. What is it?
Take a small bite and say,
"It's good." Then--
-It's cute.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I'll say, "It's good."
Then, after he goes to the bathroom,
I'll gobble it up.
It's definitely good.
-It's good.
-How is it?
-Isn't it good?
-Yeah.
-It comes out when you press it.
-Okay.
It's really good.
Okay.
It can look a little funny.
I know.
REVEAL YOUR AGE AND JOB NOW
Tell me what it is.
Age and job? All of a sudden?
-Here?
-While eating crabs?
But it's so out of the blue, isn't it?
Why reveal their jobs
while eating marinated crabs?
I really don't get the timing
of revealing one's age and job
-on our show, the Love Lab.
-Right?
How old are you?
You kept on thinking I was older.
How old you do I look?
Since you thought I was older,
I do think you're young,
so maybe 25?
Can't you go first?
-I'm 26 years old.
-26 years old?
I was born in 2001.
-Born in 2001.
-2001. Okay.
He's the same age as my younger sibling.
Really?
Yeah, he's the same age.
There's a huge age gap.
Yeah, we're seven years apart.
I was worried that
he might think I was too young
and feel a bit uncomfortable with me.
Are we the same age?
No.
Am I older?
Yes.
Are you 24?
How much younger is okay for you?
Me? Not 20 years old…
I'm 22.
22 years old?
Born in 2005?
That's my little sibling's age!
Your little sibling and mine?
I'm 22.
22 years old?
Unbelievable.
Of course, you thought I was older.
You were born in 2001, right?
I don't think that's a huge age gap.
But you said you were 25.
I thought you'd be around my age.
22 years old?
Unbelievable.
Four years isn't a huge gap though.
22 years old?
We're done for.
-We're done for?
-Yeah.
There's no reason for that.
My job is…
Wait, try to guess it.
Don't you want to guess?
-You must want to guess since you're 22.
-Give me one…
That's such a stereotype.
You're right. I agree.
-What is it?
-I am
a dancer. I do ballet.
-For real?
-Yeah.
I'm a ballet dancer.
-For real?
-Yeah.
I'm a ballerino.
I studied practical dance
at Korea National University of Arts,
and currently, I am a dancer
with Yunbyul Ballet Company.
I achieved the second place
on a male dancer survival show.
RUNNER-UP ON MNET'S "STAGE FIGHTER"
Ballerinos must express
their emotions very well.
There are at least 1,000 seats
in the auditorium.
I have to show the audience who I am
and become fully immersed
in my performance.
To give a flawless performance,
I keep pushing myself and train offstage.
When I deliver a deeply moving experience
to the audience on stage, I feel happy.
KANG KYUNG-HO
26 YEARS OLD, BALLET DANCER
I am a ballet dancer.
At that moment,
I felt like my eyes turned into hearts.
-Interesting, right?
-Yes.
-I don't look like a ballerino, do I?
-No.
Everyone says that.
He has fair skin, he's slim,
and I love that he has fox eyes.
He has a really beautiful body line.
I like people who are in the arts.
On top of that, I like sly men.
After finding out what he does for work,
I totally fell head over heels for him.
How did you end up doing ballet?
Did you see that?
She's so excited. Look at her feet.
-She's bouncing them.
-Yeah.
She's so excited.
How did you catch that?
How did you end up doing ballet?
My little sister started it first.
I naturally ended up doing it too.
What do you do for work?
I'm studying philosophy.
Philosophy?
Philosophy is less about finding answers
and more about asking "why."
I'm majoring in Philosophy
at Sogang University.
Sogang University?
That's insane.
-She looks even prettier now.
-Wow.
Ever since I was young,
I've loved theater and musicals,
so I set my goal of becoming
a performance arts producer.
I felt that producing performances
for a broad audience
required deeper thinking.
That's why I chose philosophy.
By taking on roles in planning,
production, directing,
and every stage of theater
through my drama club,
I'm steadily working toward my goal
of becoming a performing arts producer.
LEE YE-RIM
22 YEARS OLD, PHILOSOPHY MAJOR AT SOGANG
-Philosophy?
-Yes.
Honestly, that isn't so shocking.
But you're 22.
You have to be nice.
-Me?
-Yes.
Shouldn't you be nice to me?
Like respecting the elderly?
Yes.
Didn't you say that we're done for?
You seemed caught off guard.
I was caught off guard. I didn't think
a 22-year-old would be here.
This may sound a bit strange.
I…
I don't care about whether she is
younger, older, or the same age.
But if someone overlaps with
my younger sister's age,
I strangely become distant.
It's not the deciding factor,
but the moment I heard her age,
I think I put a small barrier between us.
Kyung-ho's little sister and Ye-rim
are the same age?
So what?
It does matter.
How come?
You start thinking she is
your younger sister,
so you'll want to take care of her
and say things like, "Do better."
I think that same frame has been
put on Ye-rim now too.
Okay. But you know,
it could be because she is
exactly the same age as his sister
and not younger or anything.
-I can't date someone my brother's age.
-Exactly.
I felt like there was
a bit of distance between us.
What did I do when I was 22?
Are you trying to put distance between us?
What did I do?
I really have felt that age
is only a number.
-But you didn't react that way.
-Me?
But the number two and two
is a bit shocking.
I think 24 was the youngest I've dated,
so I never even considered
anyone younger than that.
Honestly,
I didn't think a student could be on this
because of various circumstances.
Has he never watched dating shows?
There's always a college student
on dating shows.
I took some time off.
Really?
I like that you made that choice.
Stop talking like an old-timer.
I really admire that kind of decisiveness.
-Shall we clink our glasses?
-Yeah.
Chae-rin asked you
that question yesterday.
-What?
-How many people you are interested in.
How many would you like to get to know?
Me?
Right now?
Right now, there are two.
I was a bit annoyed.
But it should be that way.
And the reason why
we are all interested in someone
is just because of the first impression,
so we don't know how it'll change.
That was the conclusion everybody came to.
But…
"I don't get that"
was what I was thinking.
Can I ask who it is?
No, you can't.
-Want me to tell you?
-Yes.
The person I'm interested in?
First of all, you.
Are you curious?
Yes.
I was most curious about you.
Honestly, I'm curious about everyone.
I didn't want to fully reveal
what was in my heart.
I just want to say nice things to others.
If you don't,
both parties would feel awkward.
Am I even allowed to say?
It's…
Ga-yeon.
-But Ga-yeon is so different from her.
-Right.
They are polar opposites.
She must be nervous.
-She must be.
-And she seems older.
Oh, no. So it begins.
She knows that she's younger too now.
The whirlwind of emotions
is about to begin.
Yesterday, I was curious about
you and Ga-yeon.
Why?
What about you?
Never mind.
Why are you laughing?
Because it's funny.
What's funny?
The fact that you're 22 years old.
I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding. It was a joke.
It can be funny.
Why did you laugh?
I laughed because it was what I expected.
-The two people you were curious about.
-I see.
I do think that
I acted pretty transparently.
I don't think I spoke to anybody
besides you two.
I felt nervous rather than secure.
When I asked him a question,
I knew that I wouldn't get a reaction
to the extent that I would expect.
So it was hard for me
to ask questions to draw him out.
You know,
I realized what I don't like
about how Kyung-ho acts.
If he isn't sure of how he feels
and can't answer directly,
why would he do this?
To be honest, that was
because he didn't know her age
and he just followed his heart.
I think that's understandable.
How understanding of you.
He can do things like this.
It's understandable.
He didn't know her age.
That's not how women feel.
Usually, I'm not that honest
and I don't open up easily.
That's why it's very hard
for me to force myself to do it
since I'm not used to doing it.
Let's say I become the king.
I can choose who I want to date.
Would you like me to choose you or not?
I'd love it if you chose me.
You might want to talk to
someone other than me.
I do want to talk to someone else too
since we don't have a lot of time.
Exactly.
What about you?
Are you going to choose me again?
Would my answer change your answer?
Me?
No, it would be nice if you voted for me.
-Why?
-What?
Because you voted for me.
Well…
You'd be happy with anybody's votes.
No, that's not true.
I didn't get the feeling that
he was happy it was me.
I felt like he didn't feel
the same way about me.
And what do you… Wait, no.
How do you feel…
I think those questions
are very difficult.
"How do you feel?"
"What are you going to do tomorrow?"
The fact that she asked me those questions
came across as being very honest,
but it did make me feel uncomfortable too.
I think it would be premature
to make a decision right now.
Of course.
-It's their first date.
-Yeah.
Those questions are like the ones you ask
before the final decision.
Ye-rim likes him so much.
-She just wants to go ahead with it.
-Right.
Her ideal type is Kyung-ho.
One is smitten, the other isn't.
But Kyung-ho only put
one Heart Chip in in the beginning,
that tells me that he's not the type
-to go all-in from the start.
-Right.
It wasn't clear who had
the upper hand before.
-But now, it feels like Ye-rim…
-That's it.
-…is clinging to him.
-Yes, it seems that way.
What about you?
-Oh, no. Ye-rim looks upset.
-Would you ask me out?
The mood turned serious already.
-The air.
-Yeah, the air feels heavy.
It's too soon to be like this.
What about you?
Would you ask me out?
Yes.
You aren't curious about anyone else?
Someone you want to talk to.
I think it's more meaningful for me
to spend time with someone
I am even a little more interested in.
Understood.
I thought our feelings would at least be
somewhat similar
in terms of pace or intensity,
but I don't think that was the case.
The thing is,
if my feelings weren’t strong,
I don’t think I would
say these things or act this way.
But he could easily do it
even though he doesn't feel that strongly.
Because she's pretty.
I guess I misunderstood
and misread the situation.
I don't know why our conversation
took a serious turn.
The thing is, I'm still unsure.
It has only been two days since we met.
I get that we don't have much time
and it's too short to
get to know someone else.
Yeah, it's a bit difficult.
Is it better to go all-in on one person?
Honestly, I don't know.
If I were to go all-in on someone,
I want it to be without any hesitation.
Honestly, there's someone
I am still curious about
and I don't want to feel like
I have to force myself to let go.
Will you feel sure
if you had a conversation
with that other person?
I don't know. I have no choice
but to compare you two.
Because I don't like doing that,
I want to hurry up
and talk with that person.
I know it's very ironic.
The reason why I asked you this
was because I was really just curious.
It's not because I want to burden you
or get reassurance from you.
I think I just need some time.
Okay.
Kyung-ho may seem a bit annoying
from Ye-rim's perspective.
-Of course.
-He left too much room for interpretation.
I don't know if I can say this,
but it feels like
he played her.
-Joo-heon.
-Yeah?
Why didn’t you agree with me earlier,
but now you’re saying the same thing?
Which one?
Kyung-ho hit on her first.
But you said you understood
and that it happens.
I did think it could happen then.
People can change their minds, right?
-It keeps changing, right?
-Right.
I thought that back then.
He kept saying she was pretty.
-Her young heart must've skipped a beat.
-You're right.
-I understand how Ye-rim feels now.
-Yeah.
What? "Now?"
I hate people like that.
This is how I feel.
You do that a lot too, you know.
No, I don't!
You'd say, "This guy is my type!"
But you'd stop liking him
ten minutes later.
I'm not like that in real life!
Look, this is what I mean.
If he isn't sure about how he feels,
he should be more careful
about how he carries himself.
Kyung-ho may be thinking that he can
do whatever he wanted to try out.
Yeah, you're right.
But he's even annoying for me too.
Where did this cutie go?
-She looks like a woman facing a breakup.
-I know.
-Can't we see them in the carts again?
-Right?
Look,
-how could this not make her heart race?
-I know.
Look.
They're going down.
-She was so happy!
-Look!
This looks like a photo from the past.
Look at that. Gosh, darn it.
I feel bad.
She looked so happy.
CHAE-RIN AND DO-GEON
YUCHEON RAW FISH RESTAURANT
Thank you.
I was so hungry.
-I'm so hungry.
-I know.
Yeah, I'm so hungry.
I think you're younger than me.
Out of nowhere?
-Why?
-Maybe not?
Why?
I don't know.
What about me?
I think you could be older.
Really? Is that how you felt?
But I really can't tell.
I'm more curious about your age.
What do you prefer, older or younger?
Older.
-Older?
-Yeah.
Me too.
-You prefer someone older?
-Yeah.
That's totally unexpected.
I have never dated anyone
younger than me.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
-So you like someone older.
But you said I looked older.
Yeah.
That works out then.
What? Why are you copying me?
Why am I getting so excited?
He's so my type.
I think Chae-rin is older.
-Yeah, I think she's older.
-She gives off that vibe.
Imagine the view outside is the ocean.
-It feels like we're out on the ocean.
-It does.
Isn't it the ocean?
Are you from Busan?
You're good.
-I'm from Busan.
-Are you from Busan?
I'm from Busan.
I think dialects are interesting.
I like them.
When I first moved to Seoul,
I couldn't stand hearing people
speak in standard Korean.
Does "Hey, Do-geon" sounds weird too?
If you say that in Daegu,
it means you like me.
-"I like you."
-It's like that?
-Yeah.
Then, how do you call someone?
My friends would just say, "Do-geoy."
-Do-geoy?
-"Hey, Do-geoy."
Wow. That's fascinating.
THEIR FOOD ARRIVED
-Thank you.
-Isn't it tasty?
-It's tasty.
It's really delicious.
It's so good.
Will we get drunk today?
Maybe?
Shall we get drunk?
My heart skipped a beat.
Yeah, mine too.
Not "Let's get drunk."
-But "Shall we get drunk?"
-"Shall we get drunk?"
Drunk Date, here we go.
Shall we get drunk?
-Do you want to?
-It doesn't matter to me.
What is your ideal type again?
Someone who is understanding
and a good listener.
Someone who is calm and composed.
What about you?
I like someone who is
more outgoing than me.
When someone talks happily next to me,
I get lively too.
If there are two people like me…
"Let's eat."
-"It's good."
-"Chow time."
"Stop talking and eat."
What is it?
-We can…
-Yeah?
-…reveal our ages and jobs.
-What?
-Right now?
-Now.
REVEAL YOUR AGE AND JOB RIGHT NOW
I was so surprised.
I almost wondered
if I wanted to avoid this situation.
Without even realizing it,
I think I was scared that
he was younger.
I'm getting nervous.
Can I guess it first?
Let me start with your age.
Twenty…
five?
You think I'm 25?
Am I right?
How young are you
for you to say that?
I was born in 2000.
So 27 years old.
-Twenty-seven.
-I think you are
in the arts or sports field.
What kind?
Dance?
You're right.
You're a dancer? For real?
-Do I not look like it?
-What kind of dance?
-I majored in contemporary dance.
-Contemporary dance?
I'm a contemporary dancer.
I liked dancing since I was little.
I was drawn to the process of
expressing my inner self through my body,
and naturally ended up majoring in dance.
Currently, while continuing
my performances and creative work,
I also work as a staff member
at my alma mater, Sejong University.
I will continue to learn and grow,
constantly balancing my work on stage
with my role in education.
BODY RECIPY
BY YOO MIN-KYUNG DANCE PROJECT
I hope to become an artist and dancer
who can connect
with people and offer comfort
through honest and heartfelt movement.
MOON CHAE-RIN: 27 YEARS OLD,
CONTEMPORARY DANCER, FACULTY STAFF
That's why!
That's why she said she knew Kyung-ho.
You must be really good at it.
No, that's not it.
That's awesome.
Was it what you expected?
I did expect it.
Dancer?
When we talked about our hobbies…
I like going to performances by myself.
What have you seen?
I like to watch dance performances
in Daehangno.
-Dance performances?
-Yes.
How old are you?
I think…
you were born in 2001.
You might be shocked when you find out.
What is it? What?
I was born in 2003.
2003?
How is this…
Are people born in 2003 that mature?
Those born in 2003 are mature.
Really?
My senior in the military
was born in 2003.
You know, I can date a 24-year-old.
What? Hang on.
You were shocked when you heard
that he was born in 2003.
I was really surprised but I can date him.
But he may be all right with Ye-rim too.
-For real?
-I'm 24 years old.
24 years old?
Gosh, really?
First of all, I was very surprised
when I learned he was younger.
I couldn't hide my expression.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You're much younger than I expected.
-Am I?
-Yeah.
And I recently finished
my military service.
Really?
Yeah.
-You're on your final leave?
-Yes.
Yes, I'll be discharged next Monday.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Really?
-Finally.
I'm happy.
I'm still a soldier,
but I'd like to date someone.
When were you discharged?
March of this year.
March of this year?
Do-geoy, man. Eat up.
Gosh. To be honest, I'm really in shock.
So shocking. Let's drink.
This is so shocking.
So I just went, "Cheers."
"Shall we clink our glasses?"
I felt like
we had to keep drinking.
"Shall we clink glasses first?"
Should I act like I didn't hear that?
My hand kept reaching for the drink.
Job?
Guess.
You're an athlete and…
Yeah?
-Are you
-Yeah?
a swimmer?
-Swimmer?
-Or
golfer?
I am in the arts and sports field.
Really?
You're an athlete, right?
-I'm not an athlete.
-You aren't?
I'm not an athlete.
Why did you think I was?
I thought you were an athlete.
-You aren't an athlete?
-No, I'm not.
What the heck? You're very good at acting.
Are you an actor?
Is that the art field you're in?
-That's right.
-Stop lying.
-Are you for real?
-Yeah, I'm serious.
-What? For real?
-I'm in acting.
-Really?
-Yeah.
He's an actor.
It doesn't suit him.
-I think it suits him.
-He seems introverted.
He's more attractive now.
I am majoring in Theater and Film
at Dongguk University.
I have loved dancing and being on stage
since I was young.
I'm pursuing my dream of becoming an actor
by connecting with audiences
through the stage of theater.
During my military service,
I joined the Army performance team
and gained attention for performing
the opening part of "like JENNIE."
That experience inspired me to pursue
my passion for the stage even further.
What?
I didn't expect that.
He's practically a con artist.
Now, I hope to become an actor
who continues to deepen his craft
through diverse experiences.
PARK DO-GEON
24 YEARS OLD, THEATER AND FILM MAJOR
You may have seen me
while scrolling through Reels.
-While scrolling through Reels?
-Yeah.
It was when I was a soldier.
Isn't it something
like those people who dance
in the military?
Like a dance video
of "Hype Boy" or something.
It's Jennie's…
Wait, Jennie?
-"like JENNIE."
-Did you see it?
-I did.
Really?
-You were in that?
-Yeah.
I'm the one in the beginning.
-Really?
-In the intro.
Amazing.
Are you good at dancing too?
I took some lessons a while back
for about two to three years.
I knew it.
-You have the body of someone like that.
-Really?
I want to see it again.
I was a bit disappointed.
I wanted to avoid anybody
in the arts and sports field.
So it was a bit disappointing.
But I was hoping he'd be an athlete.
Even though he'd be in arts and sports,
an athlete might have been okay.
That thought did go through my mind.
"Okay, he's an athlete."
I guess I was hoping or imagined
that he was one.
It made me take a step back
and view him more objectively
in that moment.
Show some respect to me.
Man.
Show some respect.
Can't say the words?
I'm curious.
So shocked.
I've never dated a younger guy.
I don't think it'll be too different.
-Really?
-It may even be better.
I've never been interested
in someone who's younger than me.
Isn't that too direct?
It's very discouraging to Do-geon.
She went too far.
But there are people like her.
They don't even consider someone younger.
I want to round up everyone like that
and give them a real attitude adjustment.
-But--
-So what if they're younger?
They had a change of heart
just like Kyung-ho and Ye-rim.
I don't get it though.
She saw him as a man before.
But now she doesn't?
She didn't know his age then.
That dislike is totally unfounded.
Why would you dislike someone younger?
I've never been interested
in someone who's younger than me.
Honestly.
No interest in someone who's younger?
I've never viewed younger guys as men.
Is she putting up a wall between us
or is she rejecting me?
Those thoughts did cross my mind.
Either way, I could get her
to like me eventually.
That's the main thought I had.
So I wasn't too shaken by it.
I may be different.
-He's determined to win her over.
-Let's go!
-Yes!
-Just go for it!
He's competitive. What a man!
"I may be different."
Yeah, you may be different.
Show me you're different.
THEIR SECRETS HAVE BEEN REVEALED
Since we're sharing it…
Wow! For real?
I started over then.
We must be getting a mission.
-What is it?
-There it is.
A LETTER ARRIVES
-There's something.
-What is it?
There's something.
-Ha-yoon is excited.
-Right?
It's his first time.
-Why are you so happy about it?
-Ha-yoon.
So this is how it feels.
What is it? I'm nervous.
This only applies to use four, right?
I know. Doesn't it seem so special?
"A new chip has been added today.
Go to the Heart Room
and check it out now."
-What?
-A new chip?
-And?
-That's it.
-What?
-Let's go.
What's going on?
So there's something new.
What's this?
A new chip has been added.
-Black?
-Black chips?
"Each person gets 10 Black Heart Chips."
"This is a negative Heart Chip
that reduces your opponent's Heart Chips."
"You may use it to hold back
someone you don't want as king."
"Black Heart Chips may be used on anybody
and can be used on multiple people."
If you have used up
all 10 Black Heart Chips,
you may exchange your Heart Chips
to get more Black Heart Chips.
"If you want to exchange it,
put your Heart Chips in the glass vase
-and take the Black Heart Chips."
-I exchange it with mine, right?
-Wow.
-Negative Heart Chips.
So they can use their own Heart Chips?
To get additional Black ones.
The Heart Chips in your Heart Box
resets every day.
How should I use them?
How can I use them wisely?
It's different from a regular vote.
There must be a strategic way to use it.
There must be a reason why
this was revealed to us four first.
So how are we supposed to use these…
-Preventing someone from becoming king.
-You can use it on a few people.
You can do that with these.
Get rid of their hearts.
We can make someone king.
-Right.
-I guess?
-Since the king is made by other people.
-Right.
If someone's a strong candidate,
-we add ours to…
-If we wanted to,
we could just trade Heart Chips
and reuse them.
We already got ten to begin with.
We can use underhanded tactics
by working together.
We can definitely do that.
Those people don't know about this.
-They'll say, "What's this?"
-We're on the same boat.
-The game is on.
-It's a secret.
Let's plan it out and make it happen.
It's possible.
We could give each other hearts.
You could give it to the person you want
in order to make them the king.
-Yeah, we could.
-We could also discuss among ourselves.
We have to conspire.
HEART CHIPS BECAME TOOLS FOR POWER
You know, I'd be offended
if I didn't get any Black Heart Chips.
Do I not seem popular to you?
They must not think I can become king.
This is tough.
These things are so hard.
You know what I want to know?
Is there a reason why we have to
do all this to make someone king?
If one of the other four becomes king,
the four of us may not
be able to go on a date again.
-Then, one of us should become king.
-If we become king,
we can plan it out.
-We can match the dates.
-Let's talk about it.
We could put all the Black Heart Chips
to the person who seems most popular.
We can become king.
Let's make one of us four the king.
If one wants to go on a date
under this system,
I felt like we needed the power of a king.
The one who gets the most Heart Chips
and the fewest Black Heart Chips
becomes the king among us.
Then, who should we pick?
And how many should we give
to secure their position?
Wait, so three of us have to concentrate
our support to one person.
If we put at least 100…
Can we give it to the same sex?
You can use the Black Heart Chips
to attack the same sex,
-but I can't give any hearts to Jung-min.
-Right.
You can only put in the women's boxes.
Either you two pool them, or we do.
No, you can give it to the same sex.
How can I give hearts to…
Why would I give Jung-min hearts?
Honestly, I had a hard time understanding.
I didn't get it.
My brain was just not working.
If we want to strategize,
we have to speak up
about who we want to date.
Right.
Talk about who we want to date?
-After you become king.
-Yeah, after you become king.
We have to get together
after we become king.
We'll make one of us king
and each person can meet the king
and tell them what we want.
-Go to the king's quarters and…
-The king's quarters?
-How many Heart Chips do you have?
-I guess I have 250 Heart Chips.
I haven't used any.
Me…
I have quite a lot.
So…
You have the most, don't you?
You didn't vote yet.
Ha-yoon has the most chips
and I actually have the most chips too.
I didn't think I should tell them
the fact that I didn't vote.
I have the advantage too, right?
I thought it would be easy
to make someone king.
You know what's insane?
All the men have 200…
-250 chips.
-Yeah.
249 chips and 248 chips.
-Right.
-That's crazy.
All of them have a lot of hearts.
We have to figure out…
But if they went on a date today,
they have to give each other hearts.
Unless they loved their date so much
that they put in 200 hearts…
No one would do that.
-They may not even get 100.
-Right.
-I think I can give 100.
-It's slim.
Based on today's date?
Let's say we have 200 hearts.
We only have three nights left.
As you said,
we could use 100 to 200 hearts,
but it would become too costly
for us to choose someone to be king.
So I think,
since the average of 250
in four days is 65,
we can use that to give
someone 130 hearts.
Then, all of us can use each of
our Black Heart Chips to each person.
We'd be safe,
but we're in trouble if it goes over that.
-Then, we'll end up with nothing.
-Right.
-Then, we will…
-And…
We'll fall from grace.
65 chips each isn't a bad idea.
-65 chips each is good.
-It adds up to 130.
It's more than half of 250 chips.
-They wouldn't give 130.
-Exactly.
Of course not.
If they give it, it's 200.
If not, it's 100.
-We wouldn't get 130.
-I'm wondering.
Of the 250 hearts
we can turn them into Black Heart Chips
and keep giving them out one
by one today, tomorrow, and the day after.
Then, all I need to spend is 50 hearts.
-Even with 50, I can confess my feelings.
-That's the issue.
But you see,
why would you make
more Black Heart Chips to do that?
I thought I could stop someone
from becoming king.
Can you target that exact person?
-But I can…
-What if they could reject Black Hearts.
You might be right.
-At this rate--
-Rather than pulling down many,
it's more effective
to choose someone to be king, right?
It'd be hard to target a specific person,
but we can pick the best.
We're betting on that.
If we put in 65 hearts,
one of us can become king.
Is there anyone you want to
show your interest in today?
SILENCE
This is kind of hard to say.
What were you going to say?
-W-w-what were you asking?
-Honestly…
-How do we answer that?
-Why'd you ask?
You may have certain moments
that you cherish.
Since today's vote is too calculating…
-But there's no point in saying it.
-It's okay, you can tell me.
Once you use up our hearts,
you can show your feelings anyway.
So not today?
Ha-yoon came up with the solution,
and we all teamed up
for a little scheming.
It could be that
we promised to give each other 65 hearts.
But what if someone changes their mind
and decides to give it to another?
At least, I won't…
I'd cut ties with them.
Today… That really put me off.
Gosh, it really does.
Let's not betray each other today.
Let's put our fists together.
Not today.
-Be honest.
-At least for today.
No betrayals.
-We can turn evil tomorrow.
-Right.
-You just have to say, "Your Highness."
-What if the king goes mad?
None of us here are crazy, right?
Not me. At least, not me.
Let's not work with these two.
They're so scary.
We need four to make a king.
They're scary.
-In the end--
-I want to go out with Ga-yeon tomorrow.
I'll keep this alliance.
Even if I become king,
I won't think about causing any chaos.
I'm okay with not being the king.
Let's write a contract instead.
Get an ink pad.
-I mean it. Put lipstick on it.
-No, get a red ink pad.
Let's write it. Come on.
No reason not to.
Also,
why are you smiling so slyly?
What should I write?
Trust
and love one another.
"Trust and love one another."
Great words.
I don't think they'd know what it is
if we leave it like this.
But also,
-what if the four check--
-Check us?
You're back.
Hello.
Black Heart Chips…
What's that?
HIDING IT
They must have gotten groceries.
Really?
-No way!
-Wow!
You're the best!
Thank you.
-You got groceries?
-Thank you.
-Yes.
-Wow.
-It looks good.
-Did you have fun?
-Yes.
They got groceries.
You look a lot happier.
Jung-min can't read the room.
What made him think they looked happier?
Did you have fun?
We should take this to the lounge.
We didn't know what to get so…
You even got meat.
Awesome!
You went straight for the chocolate.
Were you craving it?
He remembered that you wanted chocolate
and got you some.
Don't you think so? He only got chocolate.
There wasn't anything sweet here.
Why would he tell her that?
How is that going to help him?
The rest can go to the lounge.
I'll make us delicious doenjang stew.
We haven't had dinner yet.
-Really?
We haven't eaten.
You haven't had dinner?
-We ate.
We had spicy blue crab soup,
soy sauce marinated crab,
-and spicy marinated crab.
-Yum!
I'm so jealous
you got to have my favorite dish.
I'm hungry.
Have some snacks.
So…
-What?
-We should decide.
Hasn't it been decided?
Who?
I think we can do that while we eat.
-It isn't that important.
-But they can hear us.
They'll come with us, won't they?
-But it doesn't matter who does it.
-Why not?
-That really doesn't matter.
Why not?
Because the king has to
do what the other three says.
But shouldn't we decide among ourselves?
Of course, we have to decide.
We have a lot of time though.
-Okay.
-First,
-the contract.
-But we might not… Right.
I won't do it
if we don't sign the contract.
Me neither. Those guys are scary.
Shouldn't we write the contract
and decide who'll become king?
-Before they come.
-It's okay.
Why do you say it's okay?
-We can take our time.
-Really?
I don't think we have a lot of time.
Who wants to do it?
Should we give you 65 hearts each?
We'll concentrate our votes.
-Then…
-Hurry.
-One of you two.
-It doesn't matter.
What should we do? Should I do it?
-Hye-won can do it.
-Okay, Hye-won.
If I become king I might…
-You'll get all these other ideas.
-Yeah.
First of all, Ha-yoon has a lot of chips
and I have a lot of chips,
but no one else knows that.
So maybe the men should give the votes.
Even if Ga-yeon isn't the king,
I thought Hye-won would
match Ga-yeon with me.
And I could sense Ga-yeon's feelings
about me a little bit.
Besides the time the four of us spent,
the two of us spent
a lot of time together,
so I felt pretty sure about it.
Honestly, I didn't want to become king.
I keep making eye contact with Kyung-ho.
They'd last a long time
and it happened frequently.
I don't know if I'm attracted to him
or he just draws attention.
I was curious.
But if I became king
and went on a date with Jung-min,
I was worried it would end up
like I was picking a lane,
so I just wanted to leave it to fate.
Where did everyone go?
They went to the lounge. Want to go?
Yeah, we should go.
Why did they go to the lounge?
I think they went to cook.
Really? Let's go.
No, go ahead. I'll be there soon.
You want to wait for me?
I'll wait.
Come inside and wait.
I had a really hard time.
It felt kind of awkward too.
Because I looked so down,
I could tell that he was
trying to look after me,
but perhaps it's because he felt sorry.
Wait, let's each make a promise.
-Promise already.
-Yeah.
Do you have a pen?
-Give it to me.
-A pen?
You won't betray us if you become king?
Do I look like I would?
I won't do it until we sign the contract.
-You said you liked me.
-I will…
-I'll get it.
-We'll write a contract--
-Ga-yeon doesn't trust me.
-I can hear everything.
That's why we're writing a contract.
Did you get the pen?
Let's do it over there.
One person at a time.
Leave it here.
When you sign the contract,
print your name, then sign it.
Okay.
Isn't it our first time in the lounge?
The two are coming.
I'll get some soju.
Should we cook the meat in here?
Can you cook it in that?
I'm worried they'll stick.
We can coat it with oil.
I put the contract
in a notebook next to the drawings
that were on display.
I hid it right under their noses.
DO-GEON AND CHAE-RIN ARE BACK
It must've been so fun!
How cool.
-I'm jealous.
-What's that?
It must've been fun.
You went on a drive in that car?
-Yeah.
-Wow.
-How nice.
-What were you doing?
-We were cooking.
-Really?
You guys looked cool
when you got out of that car.
I'm jealous.
-Didn't we have fun?
I thought no younger men.
This is too much. I'm getting so excited.
-Didn't we have fun?
I hear it sizzling.
It's going to be delicious.
-What a waste, right?
-Yeah.
I don't know if I did it right.
You're cooking the meat okay?
Aren't I doing a good job?
Did you salt it?
No.
Are you doing it right?
-I'll sprinkle some on.
-Okay.
I'm not good at grilling meat,
but I wanted to act like I was good at it.
I wanted to mess with her.
I told her to sprinkle some salt
since she didn't.
Then, I told her to sprinkle some pepper.
I started it off
with light conversation like that
and tried to grill the meat together.
I need scissors.
Shouldn't you use these to grill the meat?
Right?
What are you doing?
-Oh, no.
I know how that feels.
Her eyes are on
the back of her head right now.
Oh, no.
And Ye-rim knows.
She knows how Kyung-ho shows affection.
It's teasing.
-And messing around.
-Yeah, she experienced it herself.
He did that to her
but now it's someone else.
But the reason is only because of her age.
What are you doing?
This?
Be honest. Isn't it hard with that one?
My goodness.
Use this one.
No, you should use this.
Okay, use this then.
I think that's enough.
The pepper?
The things that Kyung-ho
was doing to Ga-yeon
became more noticeable to me.
They grilled the meat together
and joked around.
Those things were clearly noticeable.
When Kyung-ho expresses
his interest or curiosity in Ga-yeon,
I really didn't know how to take it.
For the first time, it was very confusing.
What kind of date did you go on?
-Today?
-Yeah.
We ate blue crab.
Spicy blue crab soup.
-And marinated crabs?
-Yeah.
We got groceries and chatted.
-How was it?
-We walked around nearby.
Is it different when you meet outside?
-When you meet outside?
-Yeah.
You're happy when you meet outside.
Do your feelings grow more than in here?
-Feelings?
-Does it grow bigger?
It did help me organize my thoughts.
-I see.
-Kind of.
In certain aspects,
I am more confused as well.
-Why?
-Just curious.
About my love life?
About what it's like to go out.
-You want to go out?
-Yeah.
Keep working at it.
Keep working at it?
Yeah, become king
or the king's loyal servant.
-You're dethroned. You know that, right?
-I know.
I know. I'm screwed.
I'll serve the stew for you.
Give me a bowl.
It doesn't really look like doenjang stew.
I can't wait.
It's really delicious.
A little bit of everything, please.
Please be quiet. I got it under control.
Let's eat this, Ga-yeon.
Oh, side dishes.
Put that there and share among yourselves.
Let me know if you need more.
-Should we share one too?
-What?
-Let's share a bowl.
-Okay.
I'll put it there.
-This.
-Isn't it your second time?
I know.
Thanks.
Thanks for the food.
-Enjoy the food.
-It looks so good.
What would we have done
if they didn't get the groceries?
-You're right.
-What?
Would we have starved
if they didn't get groceries?
We'd eat instant noodles.
You eat instant noodles at this hour.
Thank you.
The stew is really tasty. It's my style.
Really?
-I'll try it.
-It's very good.
To be honest, we all made it together.
Only Kyung-ho grilled the meat.
What? I helped out too.
Only Kyung-ho?
Only Kyung-ho did the meat.
Kyung-ho and Ga-yeon
sat next to each other.
I didn't want to sit next to them,
so I sat on the other end.
I didn't want to
make him feel uncomfortable,
so I kept avoiding him.
Sorry, but she's shooting
EXchange on her own.
Oh, man.
Oh, no.
It's four nights and five days.
What is she going to do now?
What did you do today?
We went to make perfume.
-And…
-The perfume.
-Did you make one another's perfume or--
-Same one.
We got the same scent.
-We went on a luge ride.
-Luge?
This?
Yeah.
-How fun.
-Do it again.
Why?
You did it so well.
Totally.
I had so much fun.
Honestly, the food
that we all made together
was very precious.
It's really tasty.
Anyway, I was happy
because I was with Ga-yeon.
Aren't you glad I got groceries?
You get a smiley face sticker.
That was satisfying.
Let's clean up and get moving.
-Okay.
I noticed that
the pot was completely empty.
We made the right amount.
THE KING RECEIVED A MESSAGE
I can't stop being nervous.
What are you most curious
about one another?
Isn't it two things?
The time has come for us
to reveal our age and jobs.
The two of you must know.
-Yes.
-We know.
How do you know?
-We told each other on our date.
-We revealed it.
I was so curious.
It would be an opportunity
for the veil to be uncovered
and reveal our true selves.
When I told Kyung-ho,
he said I was young and there was
nothing to say about my job.
That's the kind of reaction I got,
so I figured I'd think
everyone's job was cool.
That's why I felt more intimidated.
Why?
Being a college student isn't a crime!
-Whenever Ye-rim is on…
-Why are you intimidated?
Be proud of being young.
-It's a good thing!
-Exactly!
Should we start with
the people who revealed theirs first?
I am 27 years old, born in 2000.
I'm 27 years old
and majored in contemporary dance.
Dance?
And I am also working
as faculty staff at a university.
-I'm a teacher too.
-You were right.
-It really was.
-Really?
She seemed like a teacher.
I'm 26 years old, born in 2001.
I am
a ballet dancer.
-Awesome.
-It suits you.
I thought he'd be in the arts.
Being a ballerino
is such a rare profession,
so it stood out.
He seemed young,
so that was surprising.
-They both suit you.
-I want to go see your performance.
That sounds cool.
Let's all go see your performance.
I'll make sure to invite you all.
-Any performance you want.
-Nice.
That's why I already knew Kyung-ho.
-Really?
-What?
-For real?
-Yeah.
I actually knew too.
Really? No way.
-He must be famous.
-For real?
-I really knew who he was.
-Wow.
No way.
He's that famous?
He was the runner-up
on a survival dance show on MNET.
He's very talented.
All the dancers know him.
DURING THEIR FIRST MEETING
Hello.
It's a man.
-Hello.
Hello.
-Can I sit…
-Please sit wherever you'd like.
Don't all dancers know him?
I was going to pretend
I didn't know until the end,
but I just told them.
I'm a fan of Kyung-ho.
Thank you.
-Cool.
-I'm getting goose bumps.
Thank you.
I am…
22 years old.
-What?
-You're so young.
Unbelievable.
A baby.
I'm studying philosophy.
That's why you speak so well.
-No wonder you were philosophical.
-She's very sharp.
Doesn't she seem more mature than me?
When I saw her,
I thought she'd have a job
where she is seen by others.
But she was a college student
studying philosophy.
That was rather surprising.
I was born in 2003.
-I'm 24 years old.
-Hang on.
-He looks young.
-I'm an actor.
Theater and Film major.
Were you on something?
How did you know?
-You looked so familiar.
-Really?
I was discharged from the military
a month ago.
Did you dance in the military?
I danced to "like JENNIE."
Really?
-Wasn't that super viral?
-Yeah.
-Awesome.
-He was in the intro of that.
Everybody is so awesome.
I wanted to have a conversation with him.
We're both in college,
so he might be the person
I can click with the most.
Jung-min?
-I'm so curious.
-Me too.
I'm the oldest yet.
I was born in 1997 so I'm 30.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'm a freediving
and scuba diving instructor.
-Really?
-A swimming or sports instructor.
I'm a freediving
and scuba diving instructor.
Sometimes you feel free
and sometimes you face extreme challenges
while experiencing a new world underwater.
I was captivated that
which inspired me to pursue it.
I swam for many years
during middle school.
That's when I experienced diving.
It's called freediving.
I got certified in that and scuba diving.
When my students
overcome their fear of the water
and discover a whole new world,
it gives me a sense of fulfillment
and pride as an instructor.
PARK JUNG-MIN
30 YEARS OLD, DIVING INSTRUCTOR
A freediving instructor
isn't a common job.
It was the most memorable.
It suits him so well. He looks the part.
He just looks like an instructor.
He's an instructor.
Ha-yoon?
-I'm so curious.
-I was
born in 1997.
-My friend.
-Same age.
I thought I would be the oldest.
And I am a fund manager.
I work at a real estate
asset management company.
I work in asset management
at a real estate asset management company.
I currently manage real estate assets
such as office buildings
and commercial properties,
with a focus on enhancing their value.
Wow. How cool!
He looks so cool, Joo-heon.
He looks like he could help grow my money.
I studied architectural engineering…
…but when it comes to managing
real estate properties,
having a good understanding of
building structures and operations
makes it easier to respond effectively.
I identify the potential of each property,
analyze market trends, and work to enhance
competitiveness of the assets I manage.
After formal notice was given,
the eviction process was completed.
JUNG HA-YOON
30 YEARS OLD, FUND MANAGER
He looks so handsome, Joo-heon.
I think jobs matter to me.
He looked like a stick figure earlier,
but he looks like a man now.
-That's so awesome.
-That's all.
I kind of expected that.
-He seemed very achieved.
-So smart.
Yeah, that's why.
As I expected, he was a very smart guy.
He seems to live a structured life
unlike me.
-Me?
-I'm so curious.
Oh, my gosh. I am…
I thought everyone was older.
-Wait.
-Really?
-That's so funny.
-We aren't?
-I also thought all the girls were older.
-You did.
We aren't?
I was born in 1997.
-The three of us are the same age.
-We're the same age.
Yes,
and I'm the CEO of a skincare brand.
-That's what I do.
-Wow!
-Wow.
-Awesome.
I'm the CEO of
the skincare brand Elleybear.
I had been studying fine art for years,
and when I moved to the UK at 20,
I pursued studies in the visual arts.
MAGAZINE WORK STYLED BY HYE-WON
My mom studied biotechnology,
so she manages the manufacturing side
while I focus on the design side.
We work together.
From product planning to package design,
I oversee all aspects of visual branding.
It would be ideal if
it could be released this week.
The plan is to have two options available
for customers to sample.
Beyond Korea, we have successfully
opened pop-up stores in Italy,
firmly establishing Elleybear's presence
in the global market.
JUNG HYE-WON: 30 YEARS OLD
CEO OF SKINCARE BRAND ELLEYBEAR
I always admired people
who were in design or the arts.
After hearing that she studied in the UK
and designs skincare products,
I came to think she was
even more impressive.
My attraction for her grew a lot.
Gosh, there are so many talented people.
She's awesome.
Last up.
I was
born in 1999,
so I'm 28 years old.
And I am…
I think Ga-yeon is in
the beauty or fashion industry.
I work for an SK affiliate,
providing network consulting services
for corporate clients.
I am an IT consultant.
That is so awesome!
No one's job matches
the way they look right now.
There are so many shocking moments.
She looks different. That's so surprising.
She looks prettier now.
Hello, I'm Manager Park Ga-yeon
at SK Broadband.
I propose IT solutions
that meet the needs of companies,
conduct presentations to secure contracts,
and then manage the entire
implementation schedule and process.
When the solutions I’ve prepared
are chosen by companies,
I feel the greatest sense of fulfillment.
PARK GA-YEON
28 YEARS OLD, IT CONSULTANT
That's so cool.
-Interesting.
-Seriously.
It's so surprising though.
-I thought you were in the beauty field.
-Really?
I do like those things,
but I do love my job.
-Everyone's jobs are so different.
-For real.
An age gap of one or two years
isn't much of an age gap.
I don't feel that much
of an age gap with her,
so my feelings for her haven't changed.
But she has a job
that I did not expect at all.
She seemed very cool.
That's what I was thinking.
A NIGHT WHERE THEY GOT TO KNOW
EACH OTHER BETTER
THE HEART CHIP VOTE WILL BEGIN NOW
What? Multiple votes?
The Heart Chip vote
for the second day will begin now.
Multiple votes are allowed today.
You may vote for one person
or two or more people of the opposite sex.
We can vote for multiple people
starting today?
-Multiple votes?
-My head hurts.
We can vote for two or more people.
-Two or more?
-Yeah.
There's no limit.
You can even vote for four people.
But we have to give someone
the Black Heart Chips.
Yeah.
Who should we give the Black Heart Chips?
Oh, we forgot to pick someone.
THE FOUR-PERSON ALLIANCE MUST DECIDE
WHO WILL RECEIVE THE BLACK HEART CHIPS
-Let's go there.
-Then, fix this.
It doesn't work.
Since we have ten Black Heart Chips,
the four of us will use 10 each.
But we have to decide who it'll be.
Who do you want?
How about Chae-rin?
-Put 10 hearts in Chae-rin's box.
-I'll do that.
-You put in Do-geon's.
-I'll put mine in Do-geon's
Okay. I'll put mine in Chae-rin's.
You put yours in Do-geon's.
-Isn't the scent stronger on me?
-Yeah.
-Isn't it strong?
-How does it last so long?
-Jung-min will vote for Kyung-ho.
-Right.
We'll all put ten each.
And
-Ga-yeon votes for Ye-rim.
-Yeah.
Let's do that.
THE 4-PERSON ALLIANCE
HAS CHOSEN A TARGET
I should check carefully.
GA-YEON, PLEASE GO TO THE HEART ROOM NOW
Did you tell her?
Can I have some lip balm?
So? Do I do whatever I want?
Put the ten Black Heart Chips…
Yeah?
-…into Ye-rim's box.
-Okay.
Do you have any cotton swabs?
I have some.
I keep having to come in here.
What is going on with my hair?
Today, the Black Heart Chip
allows you to cast a negative vote.
There are a lot of game elements.
I'm so curious about
how those elements will affect the result.
PARK GA-YEON
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
Since I could vote for multiple people,
I voted for Jung-min
and Kyung-ho.
GA-YEON'S VOTE
26 → JUNG-MIN, ?? → KYUNG-HO
Jung-min was my top choice,
I just had a good feeling
when I thought of him.
That's why I wrote, "I like you."
I LIKE YOU!
And with Kyung-ho,
I wanted to let him know it was me.
That's why I wrote that.
And regarding what the four of us planned,
they said I should vote for Ye-rim.
GA-YEON: 10 BLACK HEARTS → YE-RIM
JUNG HYE-WON
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
I did what I was told
regarding the Black Heart Chips.
HYE-WON: 10 BLACK HEARTS → CHAE-RIN
After putting ten Black Heart Chips
in Chae-rin's box, I realized,
"So this is what it feels like."
I wasn't interested or attracted
to any other men besides Ha-yoon.
So I put one Heart Chip in Ha-yoon's box.
HYE-WON'S VOTE
1 → HA-YOON, 10 BLACK HEARTS → CHAE-RIN
Jung-min, about the Black Heart Chip vote…
Who are we voting for?
We have to decide
who we're giving these 10 chips to.
We're giving Hye-won 65 hearts, right?
-Even so--
-I…
What was that?
It's a monster.
What's going on?
We were talking about
who we should show interest in.
Oh.
Got it.
We can briefly decide that right now.
Let's just decide that now.
Then, you do Kyung-ho and I'll do Do-geon.
Okay.
Why didn't you make any noise?
I was standing here and looking at you.
Then, weren't the two of you talking?
-You two weren't talking?
-No.
EVERYONE SEEMS SUSPICIOUS NOW
-What do we do?
-Tell me.
-I'll explain.
It sounded like
the two were scheming something.
I really could have
eavesdropped if I wanted to.
You really scared me. Geez.
JUNG HA-YOON
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
I don't have any bad intentions
by voting for Do-geon.
HA-YOON: 10 BLACK HEARTS → DO-GEON
I gave Hye-won 65 hearts.
HA-YOON GAVE 65 HEARTS TO HYE-WON
I was really touched
by our brief conversation that morning.
This is Yin-Yang water.
You have to drink it in the morning.
It helps with digestion.
-It's so nice.
-Yeah.
I think it really helped my digestion
and I felt energetic the whole day.
I FELT ENERGETIC ALL DAY
THANKS TO YOUR YIN-YANG WATER! THANKS
HA-YOON'S VOTE
65 → HYE-WON, 10 BLACK HEARTS → DO-GEON
PARK JUNG-MIN
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
Since we plotted to make one person king,
I voted for Hye-won.
JUNG-MIN: 57 HEARTS → HYE-WON
And I gave the rest
of the Heart Chips to Ga-yeon.
Because it was already a given
that we would go on a date…
WE'LL HAVE MORE FUN
THAN ANYONE ELSE TOMORROW
I left her a note saying that we'll have
more fun than anyone else tomorrow.
I gave the Black Heart Chips to Kyung-ho.
JUNG-MIN: 10 BLACK HEARTS → KYUNG-HO
JUNG-MIN'S VOTE
?? → GA-YEON, 57 → HYE-WON
10 BLACK HEARTS → KYUNG-HO
Anyone would think
you're going out tomorrow.
-Where did he go?
-Who?
-Jung-min.
-Why?
-Did he leave?
No reason.
What's wrong?
Can we talk for a second?
What's going on?
What's happening?
I'm not sure what's going on.
-Maybe I'm wrong.
-What's up?
-What is it?
-This is my assumption.
While we were gone,
the four were left behind, right?
I think
they're going to make one of them king.
So what you're saying is
besides the ones that went on a date,
the four that were left
are going to make one of themselves king?
Do you want to be king?
King? It would be nice.
Me too.
Want me to invest in you?
If the tables turn because of this… Man.
-To shock them?
-Yeah.
Then,
how much do we have to spend
to become king?
-I'll just pour it in.
-Pour it in?
By the way…
-She was looking for you.
-Chae-rin was looking for you.
She looked speechless.
For real?
-Where did she go?
-She went to talk with Do-geon.
MOON CHAE-RIN
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
What's this?
"The other person's number
of Heart Chips…"
That was insane. Truly.
There was something
I never expected at all.
Gosh. Hang on.
Everyone except those four just found out
that the Black Heart Chips exist.
How am I supposed to use these?
Who should I use them on?
I thought about it a lot.
CHAE-RIN: 10 BLACK HEARTS → ??
And to Do-geon,
I gave him 20 Heart Chips.
CHAE-RIN'S VOTE
20 → DO-GEON, 10 BLACK HEARTS → ??
PARK DO-GEON
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
When I read what was written on the note,
I realized that the Black Heart Chips
can be used effectively
if people were to form an alliance
to make someone king.
And I thought Jung-min
could end up being king this time.
DO-GEON: 10 BLACK HEARTS → JUNG-MIN
I only put two hearts
in Chae-rin's box yesterday,
but my feelings for her
have grown since then so…
THE RED HEART CHIPS INCREASED
AS MUCH AS HIS FEELINGS DID
I wrote, "See you at Gireum Station."
SEE YOU AT GIREUM STATION
I live near Korea University.
Anam?
-Where do you live?
-Near Gireum.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Why do we live so close?
That's only a 10-minute walk.
I wanted her to know it was me.
That's why I wrote that.
You draw really well.
That's insane.
Can you tell what it is?
It looks like a butterfly.
Yeah, make it pretty.
-Pretty?
-Yeah.
You guys look like you're in a web drama.
Yeah, the three of you.
One of us has to win him over.
We have to charm him?
I love how you all look.
Even your outfits go well together.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Should I dress cute or hot tomorrow?
-I pick hot.
-Go with hot.
Then I'm going to go all out tomorrow.
What are you going to wear tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Something mature.
-Geez.
-Gosh!
If you're 22 years old, you're an adult!
Kyung-ho, I get what you're saying.
I get it.
But I feel so bad for Ye-rim.
She wants to wear something mature.
He keeps talking to her
because she's on his mind.
Exactly.
If you're 22 years old,
you're definitely an adult!
If you can buy cigarettes and alcohol
at a convenience store, you're an adult.
Something mature.
Mature?
No.
Never mind.
I didn't want to be king.
I just wanted to do what I was told.
Even if I became king,
I wouldn't want to burden him
so I wouldn't choose him.
But no one would choose me
besides Kyung-ho.
I really wanted to be king.
I was
so confused.
I wanted to create an environment
where I can gather my thoughts.
KANG KYUNG-HO
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
But there was something unfamiliar there.
I found out that
the Black Heart Chips were negative chips.
LEE YE-RIM
ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
I thought it was so mean.
Heart Chips are meant to be used
to express how they feel.
But if someone else deducts that,
it could cause a huge misunderstanding.
So I didn't put any in.
If I could only vote for one person,
I would have had to think
even more about it.
I went on a date with Ye-rim
and I had a great time,
but I keep getting more curious
about Ga-yeon.
Is it different when you meet outside?
-You want to go out?
-Yeah.
So when I heard I can cast multiple votes,
I felt at ease.
?? → GA-YEON, ?? → YE-RIM,
?? BLACK HEARTS → ??
Honestly,
I considered not voting for anyone.
But there's still a lot of time left,
so I thought I should get to know
someone else and talk to them more.
I'D LIKE TO GET TO KNOW YOU
YE-RIM: 1 HEART → ??
And I thought a lot about
whether I should vote for Kyung-ho or not…
The Heart Chip vote
for the second day has ended.
Female participants,
please begin checking your vote boxes.
Open your box
and only check what's inside yours.
I don't want to open it.
When I opened it,
there was a message that said,
"See you at Gireum Station."
DO-GEON → CHAE-RIN
45 HEARTS
Wow, he's so direct.
I got the impression that he wanted to
keep seeing me after we left here.
He's usually not very expressive,
but then he suddenly said something
that made my heart race.
I've never viewed younger guys as men.
I may be different.
Yeah, you may be different.
I liked it even more because
he didn't seem like the type to say that.
"Hey, he knows
how to say things like that?"
But I had quite a lot
of Black Heart Chips.
Who is intimidated by me?
It feels good.
Or is someone interested in Do-geon?
Did Ye-rim put them in?
To me, it seemed like
Ye-rim's second choice was Do-geon.
Can't you just be friends
with someone born in 2003?
Should we talk casually?
Feel free to.
-Are my dark circles really bad?
-What?
Are my dark circles bad?
-Me?
-Me.
I thought you meant me.
I wasn't asking you.
I have dark circles too.
That one vote that Ye-rim cast
-must be for Do-geon.
-It may be Do-geon.
I hope it works out.
-They look good together.
-They do.
They look good.
Maybe she wanted to
go on her next date with Do-geon.
Maybe that's why she put them in mine.
But when I think of Chae-rin, I feel bad.
It's okay. She'll meet someone else.
Kyung-ho…
wrote, "I had fun."
It was the same color as the first day.
I think I was too petty and cautious
when I only put one in the first time.
My feelings for her grew that much.
KYUNG-HO: 15 HEARTS → YE-RIM
I was relieved.
Perhaps I was being too negative.
I guess he hasn't completely let go of me.
That's what I thought.
But I had quite
a lot of Black Heart Chips.
I think I had about 30 to 40.
YE-RIM'S BOX
KYUNG-HO: 15, ??: 30 BLACK HEARTS
I think Kyung-ho put those in mine.
Maybe he thinks that
I'll choose him if I became king.
What?
Ye-rim, you got it completely wrong.
He didn't want me to become king,
so he put in the Black Heart Chips too.
I put 10 Black Heart Chips on Ye-rim.
You see,
I don't know exactly how Do-geon feels.
I thought Do-geon's second choice
was Ye-rim,
and Ye-rim's second choice was Do-geon.
CHAE-RIN: 10 BLACK HEARTS → YE-RIM
When I opened mine,
I saw that I had a lot of hearts.
But there were some Black Heart Chips.
Our plan was
to not put any Black Heart Chips
into each other's boxes.
Then why did I have Black Heart Chips?
I was just captivated by
what was in my Heart Chip box.
I didn't get any on the first day.
LEARN TO DANCE WELL, HONEYBEE
LET'S HAVE MORE FUN THAN ANYONE
I had three.
Wait, Ga-yeon may become king.
Everybody voted for her except one.
-The brown one is Kyung-ho, right?
-Yeah.
And the blue is Jung-min.
-Who's red?
-What about red?
I didn't have any yesterday,
but I have a lot today. It felt good.
"We'll have more fun
than anyone else tomorrow."
Jung-min.
We were the ones that plotted,
so he knew we'd go on a date.
That's why he wrote,
"We'll have more fun than anyone else."
HONEYBEE
"Honeybee" is from Kyung-ho.
Kyung-ho and I were drawing
and I drew a honeybee.
I'll draw the eyes right here…
You can do the tail like this.
That's so cute.
KYUNG-HO: 14 HEARTS → GA-YEON
And…
"Learn to dance well."
I think it's Do-geon.
No, go like this.
Why can't I do that?
I can't do it. I can't grasp it.
Hey, you're good.
He's better than me.
I saw that.
-Good, right?
-You get a smiley sticker.
I'd like to get to know Ga-yeon better.
I want to learn more about her
so I wrote her a note.
DO-GEON'S VOTE
45 → CHAE-RIN, 5 → GA-YEON
10 BLACK HEARTS → JUNG-MIN
Do-geon, you traitor.
-What about Gireum Station?
-And "See you at Gireum Station?"
I thought it would be nice
to chat with all of them.
Because multiple votes were allowed,
I was their second choice.
GA-YEON'S BOX
JUNG-MIN: ??, KYUNG-HO: 14,
DO-GEON: 5, ??: 10
GA-YEON RECEIVED HEART CHIPS FROM 3 MEN
The female contestants
have finished checking their boxes.
You know what I just thought of?
Since we could cast multiple votes,
we can see the connections now.
Isn't that no fun?
To be honest,
haven't we all ranked the guys?
Some relationships may be solid,
but we could get to know…
-Get to know someone we haven't yet?
-Yeah.
She doesn't want to go out with Jung-min.
-Ga-yeon?
-Yeah.
If she goes on a date with him tomorrow,
it could make them an official couple.
She feels uncomfortable since
she wants to get to know the others too.
-That's why she said that.
-Yeah.
"Isn't that no fun?"
She was hinting at it.
-What's no fun? It's so fun.
-Yeah.
It's so fun for us.
-Hye-won is supposed to be king, right?
-Yeah.
She's dropping subtle hints to Hye-won.
"Even if you become king,
don't match me with Jung-min."
Male participants,
please begin checking your vote boxes.
It's so nerve-racking, isn't it?
The alphabet T?
I was a bit caught off guard.
I wrote "T" on the note.
Because I love peppermint tea…
Think of me when you see peppermint tea.
How do I get peppermint tea?
It was fun to see him trying
to get it for me. I was thankful too.
I wrote that so he would know it was me.
That's why it's alphabet T?
-She should have written T-E-A.
-Yes, write T-E-A.
-I thought it was T from the MBTI.
-Me too. I thought it was that.
The way Hye-won expresses herself
often goes beyond what I expect.
So I figured it was Hye-won.
It was cute. She wrote, "I like you."
JUNG-MIN'S BOX
GA-YEON: 26, ??: 20 BLACK HEARTS
I could tell it was from Ga-yeon.
It suited her personality.
When I first saw "IA,"
I wondered
what this person's intentions were.
On the first day, I did his makeup
because he said
he didn't know how to do it.
Let me do it for you, sir.
Do you have dry skin? You do.
I asked him to get me
an Iced Americano instead.
You have to make me coffee.
I will.
You're my makeup artist. Of course I will.
I remembered that conversation.
I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU
I wanted to get to know Do-geon better,
so I wrote, "I'd like to talk to you"
and gave him one.
YE-RIM → DO-GEON
1 HEART
I felt more at ease
putting it in Do-geon's box.
I made that decision pretty quickly.
But I had more Black Heart Chips
than I expected,
so I had no clue who did it
or why someone would do that.
Black?
Why me? I don't get it.
Why did they give them to me?
Does someone not like me?
I don't like those Black Heart Chips.
What if you open your box
and only see Black Heart Chips?
Joo-heon, be honest.
If you didn't get any,
that would be more upsetting.
-Come on.
-Really?
"I guess I'm not intimidating!"
-Because you have none?
-Yeah.
I see it now.
I didn't have this feeling
on the first day.
But I really wanted to be king.
I didn't want to ask for any favors.
I wanted to accomplish it on my own.
Is that arrogant?
Anyway…
When I read the rules,
I could cast the Black Heart Chips
to anyone.
and I could exchange my Heart Chips
for Black Heart Chips.
As soon as I saw that,
I wanted to be closer to becoming king
even if it was in terms of probability.
I guess you can call it lust for power.
So I exchanged…
my chips.
KANG KYUNG-HO
60 HEARTS
Some may say I'm playing dirty,
but I wanted to be king that much.
I was that desperate.
TOTAL OF 70 BLACK HEART CHIPS
INCLUDING 10 PROVIDED INITIALLY
GIVING 10 BLACK HEART CHIPS EACH
I was hoping I had a bit more of
an advantage than the others.
All participants have finished
checking their vote boxes.
Did it scare you?
Moments ago, your Heart Chip votes
crowned the second king.
Please congratulate them
with a round of applause.
I had no doubt that our strategy worked.
I did suggest
that we should vote for Ga-yeon.
-Should we vote for Ga-yeon?
-Would that be better?
We were going to choose you.
Why?
-We thought it'd be better.
-When did it change?
Why did you want to make me king?
I would prefer to vote for you.
That was my plan.
-Why?
-Hmm?
I have my reasons.
I'm curious.
If Ga-yeon becomes king,
she can choose her own date.
I could find out how she feels.
That's why I gave her a lot.
JUNG-MIN'S VOTE: 65 → GA-YEON
57 → HYE-WON, 10 BLACK HEARTS → KYUNG-HO
Didn't he make an alliance?
Ga-yeon may become king.
If I became king,
my choice would be visible.
Jung-min has been openly pursuing me.
So if I choose him, everything is set.
But for me, there's Kyung-ho
who keeps grabbing my attention.
And Do-geon gave me hearts too.
It would be better
if I didn't become king.
The power to decide the date.
I really wanted to become king
because of that one thing.
I wanted to become king
and go on a date with Ga-yeon.
But what if Ga-yeon becomes king
and goes out with Kyung-ho?
Then, what about Jung-min?
Maybe they won't tell us.
Maybe not?
The second king is
Jung Hye-won.
It's Jung Hye-won.
By combining the total of the Heart Chips
and Black Heart Chips,
Jung Hye-won has become the second king.
She became king as I wanted.
The four of us did create that result.
They must have made Hye-won king.
The strategy of
the four people alliance worked.
JUNG-MIN → HYE-WON
HA-YOON → HYE-WON
HA-YOON: 65, JUNG-MIN: 57,
KYUNG-HO: 10 BLACK HEARTS
JUNG HYE-WON
112 HEARTS
To be honest, I was a bit embarrassed.
Compared to getting Heart Chips
because you're popular,
I got mine through
a lewd, manipulative
and calculated method.
So I couldn't just be happy about it.
I did a little acting.
You meant "sneaky"
instead of "lewd," right?
Oh, yes.
Sneaky.
What does "lewd" mean?
I anticipated getting
some Black Heart Chips.
But I didn't expect
to get so few Heart Chips.
I HAD FUN
YE-RIM → KYUNG-HO
1 HEART
I didn't want to make him uncomfortable,
so I just put one in.
You can make him uncomfortable.
Make him uncomfortable.
I know. You can.
I know.
He's uncomfortable? So what?
You like him.
YOU'RE LIKE A K-POP IDOL
GA-YEON → KYUNG-HO
3 HEARTS
Regarding Kyung-ho,
my eyes are just drawn to him
and I'm curious about him. That's it.
It's not that I'm interested in him
as a man.
YE-RIM: 1, GA-YEON: 3
JUNG-MIN: 10 BLACK HEARTS
KANG KYUNG-HO
-6 HEARTS
Jung Hye-won is the second king.
I had to keep a straight face
when the results came out.
But I bet it showed in that instant.
Her kingship stays intact
until the Heart Chip vote tomorrow.
I wasn't happy.
I did think that someone else
could become king,
but I added some of my strategy, right?
It wasn't some, actually.
But that didn't even work.
This is like a rollercoaster.
-Is it unbelievable?
-I'm so scared.
Now, the king's privilege
will be announced.
What if it's different from yesterday?
The second king, Jung Hye-won,
first, has the power
to decide tomorrow's dates.
Second,
she can choose one man and woman
to send to the glamping tent
for the night.
-Yes! Yes!
-Wow.
-Sending them out?
-No way.
Tomorrow's date is a one-on-one date
arranged by the king.
Everyone can go on the one-on-one date.
But one couple must go
on a date that costs 30,000 won.
-Where?
-What?
If you want to go on a date
with the person you want,
you must win the favor of the king
from now on.
The king has gotten another privilege.
Then, she can decide
everyone's one-on-on date?
Even today's glamping.
I'm going to start a mind game.
Mind game?
-Don't do that.
-Why not?
-What?
-You will all play a mind game.
Whoever loses
can choose someone and leave.
-That's rough.
-Not bad, right?
I can't do it.
-No!
-Come on!
THE 2ND KING'S BULLDOZER-LIKE APPROACH
She's the true tyrant.
Excuse me. Do you agree?
To be honest, I'm not a tyrant
like a certain someone.
-I agree, Your Highness.
-"Like a certain someone."
But please don't think of this
as a punishment…
because the tent is so beautiful.
Why don't you join the game too?
I am going to decide
everyone's date.
Hye-won's eyes suddenly got intense.
Oh, no. I'm scared.
Let's keep watching. Her eyes are…
Three, two, one.
-One.
-Two.
-Three!
-Three.
Four.
We both said three.
-What?
-"Three" was caught.
-Yes.
-Okay, let's start over then.
-What?
-No do-overs.
I don't know. I don't have VAR.
I have to catch you.
-It's up to the king.
Okay. We leave it to you, Your Majesty.
We'll follow your ruling.
She's scary.
Someone like her shouldn't be king.
I think
I regretted it a bit.
When she obtained the power
after she became king,
I could see that she did
whatever she wanted.
I was scared at first.
And…
when I say, "Three, two, one…"
I saw her madness.
…anyone can start.
I sat at the end of the couch
and thought that.
I'm so sorry.
I want to play a slightly different game.
-She's annoying.
-She's toying with us.
She's driving me crazy.
There's nothing we can do.
Dum!
-Dum.
-What's that?
Dum!
-Dum.
-Du… No!
THE TWO THAT DIDN'T SAY "DUM"
-Oh, no.
-Decide with rock-paper-scissors.
I don't know who won.
Do rock-paper-scissors.
Or should the two of you go?
Do whatever you want.
Hye-won.
All right.
Do you two want to go out?
-Why is she suddenly going off the rails?
-But,
she knows how show business works.
If she became king and said,
"What do you want to do?"
That's no fun. A tyrant is fun!
It is fun, but I don't think
it's intentional. That's what's scary.
That's true.
You know, she's so rude
to the people who helped her.
I know. Ga-yeon helped her out.
Do you two want to go out?
-We've encountered a real tyrant.
-No.
So that's a tyrant.
Shall we talk and decide among ourselves?
Isn't it better than rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
No. Hold on.
No.
What's wrong? I haven't said so.
VOIDED
You're such a tyrant.
I've never seen a king like that.
Rock-paper-scissors.
DO-GEON LOSES
Then, please choose someone
within three seconds.
I'll take Ga-yeon with me.
-This is thrilling.
-I got goose bumps.
I'll take Ga-yeon with me.
What…
HER HAPPINESS WAS
SNATCHED AWAY IN 3 SECONDS
You gloated, didn't you?
You shouldn't have gloated!
-That was such a fun choice.
-For real.
If I go down, you go down.
-He's smart.
-"If I go down, you go down?"
I've been wanting to
get to know Ga-yeon for a while.
Since I happened to lose in the game,
I thought I could use
going together as a cover.
Because Chae-rin doesn't know
that I am interested in Ga-yeon,
and Ga-yeon was already forming
a relationship with Jung-min.
So I thought it turned out for the better.
If I go down, you go down.
"If I go down, you go down?"
Nice.
Well, I suppose
I agree with it.
Oh, my. Tonight will be crucial.
This is so fun!
"If I go down, you go down."
You were my first impression pick.
That's why
I became more interested in you.
-Ga-yeon only has eyes for Jung-min.
-No.
We keep meeting eyes.
I feel like he's holding on to me,
because he doesn't want to dump me.
You make me nervous.
I can't just sit still.
He only has qualities I don't like.
Maybe it's an opportunity.
-A turning point?
-I won't use my brain today.
I think Ga-yeon is most curious about me.
One thing goes wrong
and nothing goes my way.
Then, give up?
Who'll become king?
Make me king.
Today, I'll…
I'm worried those two conspired together.
Really?
I feel like
I'm casually seeing two people.
I don't know. I just want to
go on a date with you.
Let's go.
Subtitle translation by: Ilyoung Kim
THE LOVE LAB